{
	"level1": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "1 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"2",
				"3",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "1 + 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"3",
				"12",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "3"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "5 + 4 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "5 + 5 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "5 + 15 = ?",
			"options": [
				"20",
				"5",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "20"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "3 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"4",
				"31",
				"13",
				"5"
			],
			"answer": "4"
		},
		"quiz7": {
			"question": "5 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"6",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	},
	"level2": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "1 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"2",
				"3",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "1 + 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"3",
				"12",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "3"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "5 + 4 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "5 + 5 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "5 + 15 = ?",
			"options": [
				"20",
				"5",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "20"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "3 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"4",
				"31",
				"13",
				"5"
			],
			"answer": "4"
		},
		"quiz7": {
			"question": "5 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"6",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	},
	"level3": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "1 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"2",
				"3",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "1 + 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"3",
				"12",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "3"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "5 + 4 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "5 + 5 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "5 + 15 = ?",
			"options": [
				"20",
				"5",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "20"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "3 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"4",
				"31",
				"13",
				"5"
			],
			"answer": "4"
		},
		"quiz7": {
			"question": "5 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"6",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	},
	"level4": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "1 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"2",
				"3",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "1 + 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"3",
				"12",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "3"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "5 + 4 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "5 + 5 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "5 + 15 = ?",
			"options": [
				"20",
				"5",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "20"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "3 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"4",
				"31",
				"13",
				"5"
			],
			"answer": "4"
		},
		"quiz7": {
			"question": "5 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"6",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	},
	"level5": {
		"quiz1": {
			"question": "1 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"2",
				"3",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "2"
		},
		"quiz2": {
			"question": "1 + 2 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"3",
				"12",
				"1"
			],
			"answer": "3"
		},
		"quiz3": {
			"question": "5 + 4 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz4": {
			"question": "5 + 5 = ?",
			"options": [
				"9",
				"10",
				"11",
				"7"
			],
			"answer": "9"
		},
		"quiz5": {
			"question": "5 + 15 = ?",
			"options": [
				"20",
				"5",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "20"
		},
		"quiz6": {
			"question": "3 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"4",
				"31",
				"13",
				"5"
			],
			"answer": "4"
		},
		"quiz7": {
			"question": "5 + 1 = ?",
			"options": [
				"1",
				"6",
				"15",
				"19"
			],
			"answer": "6"
		}
	}
}